[{"Response":"Very satisfied","Percent":22.6,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Fairly satisfied","Percent":49.3,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Neither satisfied nor dissatisfied","Percent":12.6,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Fairly dissatisfied","Percent":9.6,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Very dissatisfied","Percent":5.9,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Very satisfied","Percent":8.8,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Fairly satisfied","Percent":40.2,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Neither satisfied nor dissatisfied","Percent":19.0,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Fairly dissatisfied","Percent":18.7,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Very dissatisfied","Percent":13.2,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Strongly agree","Percent":7.3,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Slightly agree","Percent":25.6,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Neither agree nor disagree","Percent":26.5,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Slightly disagree","Percent":22.7,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Strongly disagree","Percent":17.9,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Keeps us very well informed","Percent":8.3,"Question":"How well do you think Lambeth Council keeps residents informed about the services and benefits it provides?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Keeps us fairly well informed","Percent":39.9,"Question":"How well do you think Lambeth Council keeps residents informed about the services and benefits it provides?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Gives us only a limited amount of information","Percent":27.2,"Question":"How well do you think Lambeth Council keeps residents informed about the services and benefits it provides?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Doesn't tell us much at all about what it does","Percent":24.5,"Question":"How well do you think Lambeth Council keeps residents informed about the services and benefits it provides?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Definitely agree","Percent":4.2,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you can influence decisions affecting your local area?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Tend to agree","Percent":23.8,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you can influence decisions affecting your local area?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Tend to disagree","Percent":34.7,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you can influence decisions affecting your local area?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Definitely disagree","Percent":37.3,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you can influence decisions affecting your local area?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Public transport","Percent":46.5,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Parks and open spaces","Percent":39.4,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Diverse and multicultural communities","Percent":20.7,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Local amenities","Percent":17.7,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"The level of crime","Percent":14.2,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Clean streets","Percent":13.1,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Shopping facilities","Percent":12.7,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Affordable decent housing for rent","Percent":7.7,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Sense of community","Percent":7.1,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Refuse collection\/recycling","Percent":7.1,"Question":"Thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the most important things that make Lambeth a good place to live? Please choose up to three things","Year":2022},{"Response":"Clean streets  ","Percent":30.8,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"The level of crime  ","Percent":24.6,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Affordable decent housing for rent ","Percent":20.8,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Refuse collection\/recycling ","Percent":12.2,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Road and pavement repairs ","Percent":8.9,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"The level of traffic congestion ","Percent":8.4,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"The level of pollution (including air quality) ","Percent":8.2,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Remove low traffic zones\/LTNs ","Percent":8.0,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Low-cost home ownership ","Percent":7.6,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Serious Youth Violence ","Percent":7.0,"Question":"Still thinking about living in Lambeth, what are the three things that most need improving?","Year":2022}]